diybookcovers.com 2018-10-02

# DIY book cover templates: Make your own cover design in MS Word

### Privacy Policy

Like most website operators, DIYbookcovers collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Creativindie’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Creativindie’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Creativindie may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Creativindie also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on Creativindie blogs. Creativindie only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Creativindie’s websites choose to interact with Creativindie in ways that require Creativindie to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Creativindie gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. In each case, Creativindie collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Creativindie. Creativindie does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Creativindie may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. However, Creativindie does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Creativindie discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Creativindie’s behalf or to provide services available at Creativindie’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Creativindie’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Creativindie will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Creativindie discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Creativindie believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Creativindie, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Creativindie website and have supplied your email address, Creativindie may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Creativindie and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Creativindie takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Creativindie uses cookies to help Creativindie identify and track visitors, their usage of Creativindie website, and their website access preferences. Creativindie visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Creativindie's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Creativindie’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If Creativindie, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Creativindie goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of Creativindie may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Creativindie may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Creativindie's sole discretion. Creativindie encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a Creativindie account, you should also check your blog’s dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Creativindie will constitute your acceptance of such change.
